Tatsuki Monji

Prague, Czechia



ttskmnj@gmail.com



+420 792733472



linkedin.com/in/tatsuki-monji-71852a13

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with more than 5 years experience. Skilled in Python, SQL, Software Developement. Have Master of Engineering focused in Information Technology from Tomas Bata University in Zlin,Czech Republic. Love to join Hackathon in free time. Won 3 Hackathons in 2019.

Experience



Back End Developer

Unirobot Inc.

Apr 2020 - Present (8 months +)

Developed Rest API and Containerize Applications.

Python, Flask, Node.js, AWS, Azure, Docker, Kubernetes, Git

QUVA Software Engineer

Quva Oy

Sep 2017 - May 2018 (9 months)

Work with SQL and Python, focused on databases and customization projects.

Python, pandas, Numpy, Jupyter, Cassandra, AWS, Docker

Software Engineer

Tech Bureau Corp.

Jan 2017 - Jul 2017 (7 months)

Developed Algorithmic trading Bot for cryptcurrency and statistic library .

Python, pandas, Numpy, SQL

Web Application Developer

NetPrice Corp.

Jul 2015 - Jan 2016 (7 months)

Developed web application backend.

PHP, Ruby, SQL, XML, Ruby on Rails

Lead Web Application Developer

Feb 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 4 months)
Developed web application backend.
PHP, SQL,XML,SOAP,Codeigniter

, : : : , : , : : ; : : 3

Web Application Developer

Nissin Systems Co., Ltd.

Feb 2012 - Apr 2012 (3 months)

Developed drive recoder web application backend and frontend both.

PHP,SQL,XML,AJAX,JavaScript,CSS,HTML,Google Maps API

Web Application Developer

goodwill planning Co., Ltd. Mar 2011 - Nov 2011 (9 months) Developed web apllication PHP,SQL,HTML,CSS,JavaScript

Education

Tomas Bata University in Zlín

Master of Engineering - MEng, Information Technology 2016 - 2019

Tampere University of Applied Sciences

Master of Engineering - MEng, ICT 2017 - 2018 Exchange study

National Dong Hwa University

Master's Degree, Computer Science 2014 - 2015 Awarded for outstanding academic performance from August 2014 to January 2015

Kyoto Sangyo University

bachelor, german 1999 - 2003

Skills

Python • SQL • OOP • Web Development • Web Applications • Programming • Software Development • Docker • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • AJAX

Honors & Awards

2nd Place - Climate-Smart City Copernicus Hackathon - AeroVision BV Oct 2020

Won Integration of data challenge - Copernicus Hackathon Brno - S.A.B.

Aerospace Sep 2019

- 1st Place Data Science Hackathon Data Science Initiative of Students of the University of Vienna
 May 2019
- 2nd Place Al Hackathon Berlin Microsoft x Red Bull Basement University
 Apr 2019
- Excellent Academic Performance 2014 Fall National Dong Hwa University
 May 2015